commentbaby.com 2008-06-21

# commentbaby.com - Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

At www.commentbaby.com we understand and recognize that privacy is important. This document outlines the types of personal information we receive and collect when you use our site, as well as some of the steps we take to safeguard information. We hope this will help you make an informed decision about sharing personal information with us. 

www.commentbaby.com is owned and operated by:  
D.B. Productions Inc.  
214 Main Street #304   
El Segundo, CA 90245 

**Personal information:**

> · We collect personal information when you register for one of our services such as our FREE Newsletter. We may combine personal information collected from you with information from other company services to provide a better user experience.   
>  · Commenbaby.com uses cookies and other technologies to enhance your online experience and to learn about how you use our services in order to improve the quality of our services. In order to allow you faster access to our site.   
>  · Commentbaby’s statistical counters may automatically record information when you visit our website or use some of our products, including the URL, IP address, browser type and language, and the date and time of your request. These counters are maintained and provided by third parties and we make no representation or warranty of their use of the information provided.  
>  You may request the names of these third party vendors for the purpose of obtaining the methods and uses of the information they provide.

**Uses**

> · We may use personal information to provide the services you've requested, including services that display customized content and advertising.   
>  · We may also use personal information for auditing, research and analysis to operate and improve our technologies and services.   
>  · We may share information with third parties in limited circumstances, including when complying with legal process, preventing fraud or imminent harm, and ensuring the security of our sites and services. 

**Your choices**

> · You may decline to provide personal information to us and/or refuse cookies in your browser, although some of our features or services may not function properly as a result.   
>  · We make good faith efforts to provide you access to your personal information upon request and to let you correct such data if it is inaccurate and delete it, when reasonably possible.   
> 

**Confidentiality  
**We do not sell, rent, or disclose your information for any monetary reason. If you subscribe for any of our FREE services such as a newsletter, you may unsubscribe or opt out at any time. When you opt out or unsubscribe, you information is permanently and totally deleted from our records.

**More information  
**If you would like more information, you may write to us at the address above.
